[{"answer": "I'm an idealist, and a romantic and a permanent optimist.", "docId": "111108pmt", "aSentId": 14, "question": "Could Newt Gingrich be the next best hope for the GOP?", "qSentId": 13}, {"answer": "She's come out in public because her name was revealed by the media, and she's decided, since her name is in the media now, that she wants to get the details of her complaint out since Mr. Cain is still denying any sexual harassment or impropriety.", "docId": "111108pmt", "aSentId": 36, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 35}, {"answer": "It certainly is not.", "docId": "111108pmt", "aSentId": 40, "question": "Is that the full extent of the alleged harassment?", "qSentId": 39}, {"answer": "It's not a question of proof.", "docId": "111108pmt", "aSentId": 47, "question": "I suppose the obvious question -- and I put this to Sharon Bialek last night, another accuser -- is that given the passage of time, being, you know, over a decade, how is anyone going to prove anything?", "qSentId": 46}, {"answer": "My client settled this matter confidentially in 1999.", "docId": "111108pmt", "aSentId": 57, "question": "Why is that?", "qSentId": 56}, {"answer": "The amount of the settlement is confidential and I'm not going to get into the details of it but there was a monetary settlement.", "docId": "111108pmt", "aSentId": 62, "question": "Can you confirm that your client was paid $45,000 to settle her complaint at the time?", "qSentId": 61}, {"answer": "Well, I think this is a woman, as Joel Bennett has said, who really didn't want to make this public.", "docId": "111108pmt", "aSentId": 66, "question": "What was the conversation that you had like?", "qSentId": 65}, {"answer": "Well, you know, I was hoping that, you know, that Sharon, my client who has been very, very brave and very courageous, you know, would inspire others to speak out if they felt comfortable in doing so.", "docId": "111108pmt", "aSentId": 81, "question": "Does this all ring true and familiar to you?", "qSentId": 80}, {"answer": "Well, you know, he seemed to shift from he couldn't recall, he doesn't know, and then it just -- you know, kind of dancing all over the place.", "docId": "111108pmt", "aSentId": 96, "question": "I mean what did you make of that when you saw him say that?", "qSentId": 95}, {"answer": "I don't -- as a presidential candidate, I don't know that there's any forum for doing that, unlike the Clarence Thomas confirmation hearings, but I would like to say that I was happy to say I hear Miss Allred say that she and her client would cooperate in a joint press conference, and I look forward to working with her on that.", "docId": "111108pmt", "aSentId": 107, "question": "Do you think it's that serious?", "qSentId": 106}, {"answer": "Well, I certainly can't speak to the credibility of his accusers and you know what happened 14 years ago, but we can look at the poll and Reuters has poll out after -- after Sharon Bialek's press conference yesterday that finds that Herman Cain's favorability among GOP voters is falling, and he's now behind Mitt Romney.", "docId": "111108pmt", "aSentId": 115, "question": "Can Herman Cain survive?", "qSentId": 114}, {"answer": "Yes, he is in big trouble.", "docId": "111108pmt", "aSentId": 126, "question": "He looks in big trouble, doesn't he?", "qSentId": 125}, {"answer": "You know, it's interesting.", "docId": "111108pmt", "aSentId": 142, "question": "Could this open up doors for these other candidates?", "qSentId": 141}, {"answer": "Well, the first step will be the joint press conference.", "docId": "111108pmt", "aSentId": 151, "question": "Joel, I mean, would you bring your client on with other women who made accusations, maybe Sharon Bialek or others if they come forward on to this show and discuss this live?", "qSentId": 150}, {"answer": "I was not aware of it.", "docId": "111108pmt", "aSentId": 190, "question": "Are you aware of this?", "qSentId": 189}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, I tell people that the tortoise is the motto of our campaign.", "docId": "111108pmt", "aSentId": 201, "question": "What do you put that down to?", "qSentId": 200}, {"answer": "Well, I think there are two things.", "docId": "111108pmt", "aSentId": 231, "question": "What is it about you that to date hasn't really electrified the Republicans?", "qSentId": 230}, {"answer": "Well, that's exactly -- it was the perfect thing to do -- for two reasons.", "docId": "111108pmt", "aSentId": 245, "question": "Do you regret that in hindsight?", "qSentId": 244}, {"answer": "Because we talked to people who were explaining the Greek view of the world.", "docId": "111108pmt", "aSentId": 255, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 254}, {"answer": "No, what I'm going to tell you is having leaders who actually take time off to go learn something is a good thing.", "docId": "111108pmt", "aSentId": 262, "question": "To pre-guess the Greek economic crisis?", "qSentId": 261}, {"answer": "Let me give you -- let me give you an example totally different than Herman Cain.", "docId": "111108pmt", "aSentId": 302, "question": "Is it unfair, though, to judge a man by his character?", "qSentId": 301}, {"answer": "It's a fact.", "docId": "111108pmt", "aSentId": 312, "question": "It is a little bit, isn't it?", "qSentId": 311}, {"answer": "I think that - I think it's important if somebody who stands up and say s a great deal of what the American news media does makes it harder for us to govern ourselves and harder for us to solve our problems.", "docId": "111108pmt", "aSentId": 317, "question": "Do you think that's a vote getter whacking the media?", "qSentId": 316}, {"answer": "This is something I find fascinating.", "docId": "111108pmt", "aSentId": 343, "question": "-- is that you're probably going to be, whether you like it or not, perceived as the anti-Mitt candidate, aren't you?", "qSentId": 342}, {"answer": "First of all, I think I am a differential to the other candidates.", "docId": "111108pmt", "aSentId": 365, "question": "So you won't be doing that?", "qSentId": 364}, {"answer": "I just said it.", "docId": "111108pmt", "aSentId": 367, "question": "How do you differ to Mitt Romney?", "qSentId": 366}, {"answer": "He is certainly much more conservative than Barack Obama.", "docId": "111108pmt", "aSentId": 382, "question": "Is he a conservative in the true sense?", "qSentId": 381}, {"answer": "Well, a majority of Americans now believe in the right to life.", "docId": "111108pmt", "aSentId": 398, "question": "Can the traditional hard line conservative values still be successful, do you think?", "qSentId": 397}, {"answer": "I think that there are exceptions for life of the mother and rape and incest.", "docId": "111108pmt", "aSentId": 403, "question": "Are you anti-abortion under any circumstances?", "qSentId": 402}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, I think with Obama, he's the best, most effective Food Stamp president in history.", "docId": "111108pmt", "aSentId": 435, "question": "And also, where do you think you differ, if you do, from the Tea Party and their aspirations in that area?", "qSentId": 434}, {"answer": "No, it was the right thing to do.", "docId": "111108pmt", "aSentId": 450, "question": "Do you regret that?", "qSentId": 449}, {"answer": "No, it had nothing to do with me losing my job.", "docId": "111108pmt", "aSentId": 452, "question": "It ultimately led to you losing your job, didn't it?", "qSentId": 451}, {"answer": "I don't worry about it.", "docId": "111108pmt", "aSentId": 462, "question": "Do you think you don't get the credit you deserve?", "qSentId": 461}, {"answer": "Repeal the Dodd/Frank bill immediately, repeal Sarbanes/Oxley, repeal Obama-care, eliminate the capital gains tax.", "docId": "111108pmt", "aSentId": 482, "question": "What would be your simple remedy to get America back to work?", "qSentId": 481}, {"answer": "I think that we got off on several wrong tracks.", "docId": "111108pmt", "aSentId": 501, "question": "I mean, what has happened to America?", "qSentId": 500}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111108pmt", "aSentId": 509, "question": "Are you an incurable romantic?", "qSentId": 508}, {"answer": "Well, let me say, first of all, I think that the recovery will begin late on election night.", "docId": "111108pmt", "aSentId": 518, "question": "What would be the first things you would do to restore American pride?", "qSentId": 517}, {"answer": "I think there are two answers to why we have fallen behind.", "docId": "111108pmt", "aSentId": 528, "question": "What would you do about it?", "qSentId": 527}, {"answer": "I think there were times in my life when I was too lonely and when I would have been much better off to have sat down with very close friends and opened up and talked through that phase of my life and tried to do things.", "docId": "111108pmt", "aSentId": 543, "question": "And what have you learned about yourself from things that haven't gone the right way?", "qSentId": 542}, {"answer": "No, no, no I'm thinking.", "docId": "111108pmt", "aSentId": 555, "question": "I'm not -- by the way, I'm not assuming this is going you have to do for a while?", "qSentId": 554}, {"answer": "I think probably one of my greatest moments of my life was going to Africa and seeing animals.", "docId": "111108pmt", "aSentId": 558, "question": "What instinctively comes to mind as the great moment of your life?", "qSentId": 557}, {"answer": "Yes, I mean, I -- when you say to me about really great moments of happiness, it is hanging out at zoos.", "docId": "111108pmt", "aSentId": 561, "question": "Would you really?", "qSentId": 560}, {"answer": "Oh, I think it was probably being on the Serengeti Plain.", "docId": "111108pmt", "aSentId": 567, "question": "What was the animal spot or whatever it was?", "qSentId": 566}, {"answer": "No, no, no.", "docId": "111108pmt", "aSentId": 575, "question": "A year from now, you seeing -- you extend the metaphor, you seeing antelope, Barack Obama, cheetah, Newt Gingrich?", "qSentId": 574}]